Shopping cart

You are $45.00 away from free shipping

You are eligible for free shipping!

You may like

[Omega 3 + Vitamin D (Wholesale)

From $227.88](https://coromega.com/products/coromega-omega-3-vitamin-d-wholesale)

[Good Eyes

$24.99 Sold Out](https://coromega.com/products/kids-good-eyes)

[Kids Omega-3

From $18.99](https://coromega.com/products/kids-omega-3)

[Omega-3

From $18.99](https://coromega.com/products/omega-3)

[Omega-3 MAX

From $24.99](https://coromega.com/products/max-omega-3)

[Pet Joint & Muscle Mobility Support

$19.99 Sold Out](https://coromega.com/products/copy-of-coromega%C2%AE-pup-packets-joint-muscle-mobility-support)

[Pet Skin & Immune Support

$19.99 Sold Out](https://coromega.com/products/coromega-pup-skin-immune-support)

[Turmeric MAX

$34.95 Sold Out](https://coromega.com/products/turmeric-max)

[Vegan DHA MAX

From $19.99](https://coromega.com/products/vegan-dha-max)

Your cart is empty

Enjoy Free Shipping Over $45

Privacy policy
==============

**Privacy Policy of The Coromega Company**

Coromega Company operates the [www.coromega.com](http://www.coromega.com/) website (the “Product”).

This page is used to inform website visitors regarding our policies relating to the collection, use, and disclosure of Product users’ Personal Information;

If you choose to use the Product, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation with this policy. The Personal Information that we collect is used for providing and improving the Product. We will not otherwise use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at www.coromega.com, unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.

_Information Collection and Use_

For a better experience while using our Service, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to your name, phone number, and postal address. The information that we collect will be used to contact or identify you.

_Log Data_

We want to inform you that whenever you visit our Service, we collect information that your browser sends to us that is called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser version, pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, and other statistics.

_Cookies_

Cookies are files with small amount of data that is commonly used an anonymous unique identifier. These are sent to your browser from the website that you visit and are stored on your computer’s hard drive.

Our website uses these cookies to collection information and to improve our Service. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies, and know when a cookie is being sent to your computer. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

_Service Providers_

We may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:

\-To facilitate our Service;

\-To provide the Service on our behalf;

\-To perform Service-related services; or

\-To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

We want to inform our product users that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.

_Security_

We value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

_Childrens’ Privacy_

Our Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under the age of 13. In the case we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to do necessary actions.

_Contact Us_

If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us at support@coromega.com.

Invalid Password

 [Enter](javascript:void(0);)

Free shipping over $45

Subscribe & Save 15% Every time!

Over 5,000 5-Star Amazon Review

Quick links

Join the Community

Be the first to know about new product launch, promotions and more!

Sign up

© 2024 [Coromega](https://coromega.com/).

{"themeColor":"#ed7b34","iconColor":"#ed9259","showLogo":false,"topBottomPosition":25,"rightLeftPosition":25,"iconSize":"small","iconCustomSize":50,"position":"bottom-right"}
